[

](https://terra.do/)

Main Menu

    CLIMATE FELLOWSHIP
    
    Climate Change: Learning for Action
    -----------------------------------
    
    Our climate fellowship is a 12-week intensive program covering climate science, impacts, and solutions, designed to get you working on climate.
    
    * **Applications close on November 22, 2024**

    Apply now
    
    Meet changemaking alumni
    ------------------------
    
    See profiles of alumni who have leveraged their skills, passion, and Terra.do training to secure new positions in the climate sector.

    Attend open houses
    ------------------
    
    Ask alumni about their climate career journeys and learn how best to leverage the climate fellowship at live, online Q&A events.

    Understand critical areas of the climate landscape
    --------------------------------------------------
    
    Explore actionable solutions in several areas of climate through cohort-based courses.

    ##### SOLUTIONS-BASED COURSES

    ##### CORPORATE CLIMATE COURSES

    Climate learning for your organization — upskill and mobilize employees. 

* Resources
    
    Climate job board
    -----------------
    
    Explore 40,000+ climate jobs from 7,500+ companies across functions and geographies.

    The Climate Switch
    ------------------
    
    Get expert insights, inspiring stories, and actionable tips in your inbox.

    Blog: It Takes a Planet
    -----------------------
    
    Climate articles from real world changemakers: a global resource of climate information.

    New
    
    [
    
    ](https://www.terra.do/#resources)
    
    ###### [Climate Swings – A Biweekly Podcast on Climate Action from Terra.do Fellow | **Listen Now**](https://www.terra.do/#resources)

    About us
    --------
    
    Our mission is to get 100 million people to work on climate this decade.

    Join our team
    -------------
    
    Become the enabler that gets millions of people to work directly in climate change.

    Talk 1:1
    --------
    
    Interested in climate action? Let’s chat about how our climate fellowship can help you find your path.

    Open house
    ----------
    
    Q&A with Climate Change: Learning for Action course instructors and alumni.

Privacy policy
==============

Updated: March 2024

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at TERRA.DO INC. (“Company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at PRIVACY@TERRA.DO.

When you visit or access our websites, applications and/or social media properties (which we refer to collectively as the “Sites”) or use or participate in our products, applications, courses, forums, events, sales and marketing activities or other services (which we refer to collectively as our “Services”), you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy policy, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use and disclose it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our Services.

This privacy policy applies to all personal information collected from or through our Sites and Services. Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.

Table of contents
-----------------

1. [WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?](#1)
2. [WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE AND HOW WILL IT BE USED?](#2)
3. [DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?](#3)
4. [HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?](#4)
5. [IS YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED INTERNATIONALLY?](#5)
6. [WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?](#6)
7. [HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?](#7)
8. [DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?](#8)
9. [WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#9)
10. [CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES](#10)
11. [DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#11)
12. [DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?](#12)
13. [HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?](#13)
14. [HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](#14)

#### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

_In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our Services, when registering or signing up for any Services and when participating in activities on the Sites or using the Services (such as when you contribute input during one of our courses or events, posting messages in our online forums or enter competitions, contests or giveaways) or otherwise contacting us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the choices you make and the particular Services and associated features you use. The personal information we collect can include the following:  

* Your name, address, email, phone number and/or other contact information.
* Your image, likeness, voice, professional and personal biographical information, and/or other personal information and characteristics, including when we record courses, presentations or events that you are participating in, or record video conference sessions associated with such Services. If you do not want your image, voice and likeness to be recorded in such manner, you should change your screen alias, turn off your camera and refrain from speaking for the particular video conference or other recorded portion of the Services (using only the chat feature to communicate).
* Social Media Login Data. We may provide you with the option to register using social media account details, like your Facebook, Twitter or other social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will collect the information described in the section called “HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS” below.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

#### Information automatically collected

_In Short: Some information — such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our site._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Site. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Sites and Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

#### 2\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE AND HOW WILL IT BE USED?

_In Short: We only share and use your information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide and operate the Sites and Services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations._

We may process, use or share data based on the following legal basis:

1. Consent: We may process, use and share your data if you have given us specific consent to process, use or share your personal information for a specific purpose or disclose your information to a specific recipient or the public.
2. Provide and Operate Sites and Services: We may process and use your personal information to operate, test develop, distribute and provide our Sites and Services.
3. Legitimate Interests: We may process and use your information when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.
4. Performance of a Contract: Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process, use and share your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.
5. Legal Obligations: We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).
6. Vital Interests: We may use and disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

More specifically, we may need to process or use your data or share your personal information in the following situations:  

1. Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data and information with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such data or information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites or through the Services, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Sites or Services over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.
2. Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
3. Third-Party Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites or use the Services. These companies may use information about your visits to our Sites and other websites that are contained in web cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
4. Affiliates. We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.
5. Business Partners. We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.
6. Other Users. When you share personal information or otherwise interact with public areas of the Sites or the Services, such personal information may be viewed or accessed by all users and visitors to the applicable Sites and/or Services, and may be publicly distributed outside the website in perpetuity. If you interact with other users of Sites and Services or register through a social network (such as Facebook), your contacts on the social network will see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of your activity, communicate with you within the Sites and/or Services, and view your profile.
7. Publication of Certain Recordings. Recordings of our courses, presentations and events that you have participated in may contain your name, image, likeness and voice, and such recordings may be shared with and made accessible to not only other users and visitors but also to the general public (for example, when a particular class, session or event, or link thereto, is posted on YouTube and thereby become accessible to the general public).

#### 3\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

_In Short: We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Policy.

#### 4\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?

_In Short: If you choose to register or log in to our services using a social media account, we may have access to certain information about you._

Our Sites offers you the ability to register and login using your third party social media account details (like your Facebook or Twitter logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, e-mail address, friends list, profile picture as well as other information you choose to make public.

We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this Privacy Policy or that are otherwise made clear to you on the Site or in the Services. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy policy to understand how they collect, use and share your personal information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

#### 5\. IS YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED INTERNATIONALLY?

_In Short: We may transfer, store, and process your information in countries other than your own._

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are accessing our Site or Services from outside this country, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in our facilities and by those third parties with whom we may share your personal information (see “WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?” above), in this country and other countries.

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, then these countries may not have data protection or other laws as comprehensive as those in your country. We will however take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

#### 6\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?

_In Short: We are not responsible for the safety of any information that you share with third-party providers who advertise on or are linked to, but are not affiliated with, our Sites._

The Site and Services may contain advertisements or links from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may lead to or link to other websites, online services or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the website. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

#### 7\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

_In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will require us keeping your personal information for longer than 2 (two) years.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to use or process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

#### 8\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?

_In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using or visiting the Sites or the Services you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of such Sites and Services . If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at privacy@terra.do.

#### 9\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

_In Short: You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.htm.

**Account Information**  
If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can avail yourself of the following procedures:

* Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements. In addition, some of your personal information that has been embedded in our courses, presentations or events (if any), and recordings of your name, image, voice and likeness made in connection with certain Services as described above, may be retained in connection with our offering, display and distribution of our Sites and Services in the ordinary course of our business.
* Opting out of email marketing: You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided below. You will then be removed from the marketing email list – however, we will still need to send you service-related emails that are necessary for the administration and use of your account. To otherwise opt-out, you may email us at privacy@terra.do.

#### 10\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy policy.

#### 11\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

_In Short: Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information._

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with whom we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

 If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with Terra.do, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on Terra.do. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on Terra.do, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

#### 12\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?

_In Short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

#### 13\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?

If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at privacy@terra.do or by post to:

Terra.do Inc.  
56 DUDLEY LN, APT 106  
STANFORD, CA 94305

#### 14\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

Based On The Laws Of Some Countries, You May Have The Right To Request Access To The Personal Information We Collect From You, Change That Information, Or Delete It In Some Circumstances. To Request To Review, Update, Or Delete Your Personal Information, Please Submit A Request Form By [Clicking Here](https://atisundar.typeform.com/to/T2QosHLK). We Will Respond To Your Request Within 30 Days.

[

](https://terra.do/)

Join our mission of getting 100 million people to work directly on climate in this decade.

#### About us

#### Talk to us

#### Climate fellowship

#### Climate Learning for Enterprise

Climate learning for your organization — upskill and mobilize employees.

#### Community

#### More from Terra.do

#### Solutions-based courses

#### Corporate climate courses

#### Careers

#### Downloads

[

](https://apps.apple.com/us/app/terra-do-climate-jobs-work/id1618165862)

[

](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=app.terra.hubbleBeta.prod&hl=en_CA&gl=US&pli=1)

© Copyright 2024 | Terra.do All rights reserved​ | [Sitemap](https://www.terra.do/sitemap/)
